







Summary

Jump to Section

Marketing professional with an experience of 6 years in Data Analysis, Product Development, product roadmap, Service delivery, Business Planning, Product Strategy, Release Management, JIRA, Trello, Rally, Kanban expertise in product enhancements, competitive analysis and product positioning. Disruptive Marketing Strategy involving ATL/BTL and Product/Pricing innovation, Managing Distribution expansion & efficiencies, Distribution formats basis ROI & channel efficacy and Brand & Marcom. Led various transformational projects across various functions, like Telecom sector, Customer Support, B2B & Mobility sales.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Work Authorization

Work Experience

ADP Inc. as Senior Product Manager -IT Jun 2017 to Till Date

Leading a cross product portfolio initiative across ADP to reduce paper consumption across all clients, tapping a potential \$29 MM cost impact

Product Manager - ADP Reports & Analytics - New Jersey, USA (Aug 2019 - Oct 2020)

Spearheaded the product vision and roadmap for ADP's Reports & Insights platform, reviewing over 3500+ feedbacks collected from multiple sources

Collaborated with Customer Support, Strategy, Engineering, and Sales teams to define product OKR's and focus areas around reducing client calls, improving user self-service and increasing data monetization

Built a web connector to integrate ADP Analytics with Tableau and Power BI, growing channel sales by 9% Streamlined the product launch strategy for new Reports & Analytics features, effectively growing pilot clients engagement by 14%

Worked with a team UX designers to re-imagine the customer journey on the Workforce Insights card, using A/B testing, thereby increasing user-traffic by 21%

Launched an in-product embedding feature, connecting Insights to HCMAnalytics modules, increasing feature clickthrough rate (CTR) by 16%

Led the exploration and development of Top Performer storyboard feature for manager & executive users using machine learning to predict high flight-risk top performing employees, increasing subscription by 11%

ADP Inc

Product Manager - ADP Data Products - New Jersey, USA (Jul 2018 - Jul 2019)

Designed a consolidated product feedback system to collate feedbacks across multiple channels, improving client reach out by 37%

Interviewed over 40+ end-users to validate the hypothesis of an automated report scheduling & email feature, reducing the server load by 28%

ADP Inc.

Product Manager Intern- ADP Benefits - New York, USA (Jun 2017 - Aug 2017)
Conducted and led an in-depth competitive intelligence study to identify market trends & strategy for ADP Benefits product portfolio

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Tata Consultancy Services as Information Technology Analyst Oct 2013 to Jun 2016

Devised post-acquisition migration strategy for a European client, successfully migrating 150,000 + invoices

Onmobile Global as Operations Engineer -Telefonica Sep 2011 to Sep 2013

Led the development of an e-lottery based B2C app, which led to a 43% increase in monthly active users (MAU)

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics Communication and Computer Programming) from Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIU) in 2011

PG: MBA/PGDM (Marketing and Business Analytics) from University of Georgia, Terry College of Business - Atlanta, GA in 2018

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Lean Six Sigma Green Belt

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Agile & Scrum Framework		
KANBAN		
Google Suite, JIRA, Trello, Rally		
Microsoft Excel, Google Suite		
TABLEAU		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

US Work Status: Authorized to Work in the US

Countries: India, Canada, Germany

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.